So the next AI tool that we're going to be talking about, the next AI design tool that we're going to be talking about
It's called Fatour. So Fatour is an online photo editing software as you see
developed by
Shang-Joo
every merging science and technology code if I'm right with them. Hey, and it's built in China, obviously
It offers a complete set of tools as you see for both individuals and companies
to effortlessly edit photos and design graphics. So as you see the software uses a drag-and-drop yet and
You can see find some history about it over here
But the point here is that in this lecture. We're just going to go through the
artificial intelligence tools that Fatour provides us with and as you see over here
we can see that we have a private company
in the industry software and the website as he is footour.com and clip-fly.com